Slow down! The paper won't be
sold out at 1:00 in the morning.
조이, 좀 천천히 가
새벽 1시에 신문이 동나진 않아
I'm excited!
I've never been reviewed before!
흥분돼서 그래
신문 비평은 처음이잖아
어쩜 왕 흉내를 그렇게
잘 내니? 감동했어
You were so amazing as the king!
I'm really impressed.
다음부터는 꼭 속옷을
입고 연기해
But you know what?
You might wanna wear
underwear next time.
When you sat on the throne,
you could see your...
왕좌에 앉는 장면에서
네 거시기가 보였거든
... royal subjects.
Here it is! Here it is!
여기 나왔어!
'풋내기 감독보다
더 형편없었던 것은'
"The only thing worse than
the mindless adolescent direction...
...was Joseph Tribbiani's disturbingly
unskilled portrayal of the king."
'조이 트리비아니의
왕 연기였다'
한 개인의 생각일 뿐이야
피비, 네 걸 읽어 봐
Okay, look.
That is one guy's opinion.
All right?
Pheebs, read yours.
'풋내기 감독보다
더 형편없었던 것은... '
"The only thing worse than
the mindless, adolescent direction"
다른 신문 가진 사람 없어?
Anybody have a different paper?
로스, 네가 읽어 봐
Ross, read yours.
싫어
I don't want to.
다들 네 연기의 진가를
몰라서 그래
Joey, they don't know
what they're talking about.
이런 비평이 맞을지 몰라
Maybe they do.
10년 동안 무명인 걸 보면
알잖아
I've done this 10 years and I'm
nowhere. There's gotta be a reason.
다 이유가 있는 거라고
여기까지 온 게 어딘데!
Come on, you're just
paying your dues.
No, no, no. It's too hard.
아냐, 너무 힘들어
It's not worth it. I quit.
그럴 가치도 없고
그만두겠어
Come on, Joey!
- 그런 소리 마, 조이
- 잠깐만, 여기도 실렸어
Wait, wait one minute.
Wait a minute.
I believe this will change your mind.
이걸 읽으면
생각이 달라질걸?
"ln a mediocre play, Joseph Tribbiani
achieved brilliant levels of
'평범한 작품에서 보인 조이의
새로운 연기력, 그건 바로... '
Continued on page 153.
'155페이지에서 계속'
'유치함이다'
sucking."
The One With Russ
I used to want to be a vet.
난 수의사가 꿈이었어
Then I found out you have
to put your hands into cows.
소 내장 같은 걸 직접
만져야 하는 줄은 몰랐거든
나 왔어
- 어서 와, 괜찮아?
- 응, 오늘 너무 힘들었어
Are you okay?
Just a tough day at work, you know?
공룡이 넘어지면서
꼬마가 안에 갇혔거든
Stegosaurus fell over, trapped a kid.
이 재킷 많이 본 건데...
바비의 것이잖아!
I know this jacket.
This is Fun Bobby's jacket!
Where is he?
He's here, isn't he?
어디 있어?
여기 와 있지?
- 아마도
- 장난치지 말고 빨리
-Maybe.
-Don't toy with me.
Geller!
- 겔러!
- 바비!
Hey, Fun Bobby!
Hey! You been working out?
- 요새 운동 좀 했나 보네?
- 전혀! 정말 웃긴 친구야!
Not at all.
I love this guy!
I'm psyched to hear
you're back with Monica.
동생이랑 다시 사귄다며?
정말 잘됐어
- 우리는 연인!
- 무슨 얘기들 했어?
-You and me both!
-So what'd I miss?
We were trying
to make Joey feel better.
조이 기분 좀 띄워 주려고
Need me to pick you up?
- 내가 들었다 놔 줄까?
- 아니, 됐어, 괜찮아
No, I'm all right, man.
- 아냐, 내가 들어 줄게!
- 아냐, 진짜 싫어...
No, I'm picking you up!
No, seriously.
I don't need you to
좋아, 효과 만점이다
It still works!
Before I go, does anybody else
need to be picked up?
좋아!
나 가기 전에
들리고 싶은 사람?
I'm still gonna go.
가야겠군
나중에 봐
See you later, babe.
Public display of affection coming up.
You can avert your eyes.
애정표현이 시작될 테니
모두 눈 돌려 줘
- 갈게
- 나중에 봐
See you.
- 정말 괜찮은 남자야
- 그렇지?
Fun Bobby is so great.
Oh, isn't he?
이번엔 잘될 것 같아
날 즐겁게 해주거든
I think this time it may work with him.
He makes me feel so good.
직장, 애인 모두 잃고
두 달 간 정말 힘들었는데
I've been feeling so lousy lately.
No job, no boyfriend.
Well, at least my cup is half full.
컵이 반쯤 찬 것 같아
Half full of love!
반쯤 찬 사랑이여!
For our two-week anniversary,
he's taking me to his cousin's cabin.
만난 지 2주 기념으로
친척 오두막에 갈 거야
Cabin of love!
사랑의 오두막이여!
We went through
a lot of wine tonight.
오늘 우리 와인 엄청 마셨어
정말?
난 두 잔 마셨는데
I only had two glasses.
I had a glass.
난 한 잔
Two.
- 난 두 잔
- 나도 한 잔
I had one glass.
난 이걸로 한 잔 마셨어
I had a mug full in this...
이름하여 '박물관에서 건진
뼈로 만든 잔'
... I-got-boned-at-the-
Museum-of-Natural-History mug.
그럼 두 병 정도일 텐데
어째서 5병이나 나왔지?
Okay, so that's what?
Two bottles.
And yet somehow we went through five?
So what?
So he drank a lot tonight.
와인 좀 많이 마셨다고
그게 뭐 대수야?
지금 생각해 보니까
Now that I think about it,
I don't think...
술 안 마신 바비를
본 적이 없어
...I've ever seen Fun Bobby
without a drink.
맞아, 너희들 못 느꼈니?
And did you notice how
he always starts his stories with...
항상 하는 말 있잖아
... "Okay, I was so wasted!"
or "Oh, we were so bombed!"
'필름이 끊기게 마셨어
엄청 퍼마셨어'
'깨어 보니 어느 동네
쓰레기장이더라고'
"So I wake up and I'm in
this dumpster in Connecticut!"
Have you been with him
when he wasn't drinking?
모니카, 바비 만났을 때
술 안 마신 적 있었어?
We just happen to go to a lot
of places where you might drink.
항상 술을 마셔야 하는
장소에 갔었거든
How do you go to a wine-tasting
without having a drink?
와인행사장에 가서
안 마실 수는 없잖아?
클럽하고... 동물원도
Or to a club, or to the...
...zoo.
Rach, does this have nonfat milk?
이거 탈지 우유야?
몰라, 한번 마셔 봐
I don't know, taste it.
- 아냐
- 입 대서 못 물러
Too late, you already had some.
What do you say
we make these coffees lrish?
아이리시 커피로 만들어
마셔 볼까?
케이크!
Cake!
Yeah, we're gonna get some cake.
참, 케이크를 먹기로 했지
It seems like you've been making
an awful lot of stuff "lrish" lately.
요즘 아이리시 커피를
많이 마시네
I'd make them Belgian, but the waffles
are hard to get into that flask.
벨기에 식도 괜찮은데
와플을 병에 넣기 힘들어서
- 바비...
- 알았어
Yeah, okay.
내가 참견해야 할지 아닌지
잘 모르겠지만...
Maybe it's none of my business.
Or maybe it is, I don't know.
I'm worried about you.
자기가 걱정돼서 그래
This isn't the first time somebody
said something to me about this.
내가 그런 얘기
한두 번 들은 줄 알아?
그럴 때마다 난 이렇게 답하지
But I always made excuses,
like "I'm just a social drinker."
'그래, 나 술 좋아해'
'오늘 빨간 날이잖아'
Or "Come on, it's Flag Day!"
So, what are you saying now?
지금은?
I guess I'm saying...
내 말은...
술 끊도록 노력할게
... I'll try and quit.
I like that you worry about me.
걱정해 줘서 고마워
무슨 얘기들 했어?
So, what's going on?
I am gonna try and quit drinking.
나 술 끊기로 했어
Oh! Why?
왜?
- 잘 있었어?
- 어서 와
Guess who's back in show biz!
누가 다시 연예계로
컴백했게?
Lorne Greene?
로렌 그린?
No. You know why?
Because he's dead.
아니, 그는 컴백 못해
죽었거든
Oh, no.
저런!
This is gonna seem bittersweet now...
착잡하기는 하겠지만
바로 조이야!
... but Joey, that's who!
매니저가 '우리의 삶'에
오디션이 들어왔대!
My agent called with an audition
for Days Of Our Lives!
죽인다!
Kick ass!
그럼 축하파티를 해야지
시트콤처럼 해야 하나?
We have to celebrate!
We should do a soap opera theme.
그래, 우리 다같이 자고 나서
전부 기억상실증 걸리는 거야
We could all sleep together,
then one of us could get amnesia!
When do you get off?
We'll do something tonight.
레이첼, 몇 시에 끝나?
오늘 파티할 건데
근무시간은 끝났는데
선약이 있어서
Well, actually, I'm already done.
But I kind of got plans.
You have other friends?
다른 친구들이 있어?
사실... 데이트가 있어
I have a date.
What?
- 뭐?
- 남자하고?
With a man?
What's so strange
about me having a date?
내가 테이트하는 게
뭐가 그리 이상해?
로스는?
What about Ross?
You're still mad
because he made that list?
그 목록 때문에
아직도 화 안 풀렸어?
아냐, 화 안 났어
No, no, I'm not mad at him.
I'm not really "anything"
at him anymore.
이제 로스한테는
관심도 없다고
- 무슨 소리야?
- 모르겠어
-What are you talking about?
-I don't know.
Whatever I was feeling, I'm...
옛날의 그런 감정들이
없어졌어
... not.
But you guys came so close.
둘이 잘될 수 있었는데
너희들에겐 미안하지만
I'm sorry. You'll have
to get used to the fact...
더 이상 나와 로스를
관련지어서 생각하지 마
...that I will not be dating Ross.
저기 왔다, 어서 와
Here he is.
얘들아, 여긴 러스야
Guys, this is Russ.
안녕?
재능 없다는 게 아냐
재능은 있어
I'm not saying you're not talented.
You're very talented.
But with the bird dead and all,
there's very little act left.
새가 죽어서
연기자가 필요 없다고
Honey, give me a break, will you?
뭘 그런 것 같고 그래
나중에 얘기하자고
I'll talk to you later.
There's my favorite client!
내 최고의 고객이 왔군
So tell me, darling,
how was the audition?
말해 봐
오디션은 어땠어?
I think it went well.
I got a callback for Thursday.
잘된 것 같아요
목요일에 다시 오래요
Joey! Have you ever
seen me ecstatic?
내가 기뻐 날뛰는 것
본 적 있어?
- 아뇨
- 그럼 잘 보라고
Well, here it is.
알았어요
Okay! Listen, there's something
I want to talk to you about.
할 얘기가 있어요
캐스팅 담당이...
The casting lady
Oh, isn't Lori a doll?
- 로리 정말 괜찮지?
- 그래요
She's great.
But I kind of got the feeling that
she was sort of coming on to me.
그런데 뭐랄까 내게...
추파를 던지는 것 같아요
And I definitely would get the part
if I were to, you know....
배역을 따내려면 그걸...
If I sent the little general in.
장군님이 손을 써주셔야
할 것 같아서요
알겠어
당장 전화를 걸어서
I see! Well, I'm just gonna
put in a call here...
...and we'll find out what's going on
and straighten it out.
무슨 일인지 알아보겠어
네, 로리 좀 부탁해요
Lori, please.
Hi, darling!
안녕, 로리!
택시기사 역 맡은
조이 트리비아니 어때?
How about Joey Tribbiani
for the part of the cab driver?
Isn't he terrific?
Okay, doll, talk to you later.
알았어, 나중에 통화해
한번 자 줘야겠어
You're gonna have to sleep with her.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 바비 때문에
-What's the matter?
-Fun Bobby.
What? Isn't he sober?
왜, 술도 안 마셨는데
술은 안 마시는데
Oh, he's sober all right.
Turns out that Fun Bobby
was fun for a reason.
바비가 재미있었던 것에
이유가 있더라고
All right, here you go, sweetie.
커피 나왔어, 자기
Thanks. You wanna
hear something funny?
고마워
- 웃긴 얘기 해줄까?
- 어머 좋아라!
Oh, God, yes!
There are no hardware stores open
past midnight in the Village.
자정이 되면 모든 철물점이
문을 닫아
That is funny.
참 웃긴다
I needed to buy a hammer and I'm out
walking around the neighborhood.
망치를 사려고 동네를
다 돌았던 적이 있는데
But apparently...
새벽에 문 여는
철물점이 없더라고
...there are no hardware stores open
past midnight in the Village.
- 자기, 면접 보러 가야지
- 그래
Don't you have to
be at your interview?
Oh, yeah.
- 나중에 봐
- 잘 가
See you guys.
Bye...
...ridiculously dull Bobby.
바비가 바보가 됐네
Oh, my God.
맙소사!
He's not that bad.
그리 나쁘진 않잖아
나쁘지가 않아?
망치 얘기 못 들었니?
Not that bad?
Did you not hear the hammer story?
Okay, don't get all squinky.
알았어, 왜 나한테 눈을
부릅뜨고 난리야
직접 경험해 봐야 아는
그런 얘기일 수 있잖아
Maybe it's the kind of story
where you had to be there.
난 이제 발목 잡혔어!
But I'm gonna be there!
For the rest of my life.
술까지 끊게 만들었는데
차버릴 순 없잖아
I can't dump him. I made him
quit drinking. I made him dull!
나 때문에 바보가 됐다고!
그렇게 생각하지 마
원래 바보 같은 성격을...
Don't say that.
He's probably always been dull.
You just, you know...
네가 불러낸 거지
...set it free.
- 안녕
- 어서 와, 로스
Hey, Ross.
안녕, 러스
Hi, Russ.
I've got two more tables
to clean, and then we'll go.
- 두 테이블만 더 치우면 돼
- 알았어
I'll just sit here and...
그 동안 얘기나 하고 있지 뭐
...chat with your...
...friend-type people.
네 친구 같은 사람들하고
Rachel?
레이첼?
- 안녕?
- 그래, 안녕
So, you know what
you're doing, right?
네 행동을 네가 잘 알지?
Waitressing?
- 테이블 청소?
- 그래, 아니 내 말은...
Well, yeah. But, no.
I mean....
Doesn't Russ just
remind you of someone?
러스가 누구랑 많이
닮지 않았어?
Bob Saget?
- 밥 사겟?
- 맞아!
Oh, yeah!
아니, 그게 아냐!
No, no, no!
- 안녕
- 세상에!
Oh, my, oh!
왜 그래?
What's wrong?
화가 났나 봐
She's upset because...
아침에 모르고 거미 붙은
식빵에 버터 발라먹었대
...she buttered a spider
into her toast this morning.
All right.
그렇구나
걱정하지 마
Listen, Pheebs.
This is gonna be okay.
Ross, Russ.
Russ, Ross.
로스, 이쪽은 러스
러스, 이쪽은 로스
- 안녕
- 안녕!
혹시 레이첼의 친구?
Are you a friend of Rachel's?
Yes. Yes, I am.
응, 그쪽도 레이첼 친구?
Are you a friend of Rachel's?
난 뭐랄까...
Actually, I'm kind of a...
한마디로 표현하면
...you know...
레이첼과 데이트 같은 거
하는 상대지
...a date-type thing...
...of Rachel's.
A date?
- 데이트?
- 맞아, 레이첼하고
I'm her date.
Oh! Oh, you're a....
그러니까...
아, 데이트를 한다고
Oh, you're the date.
괜찮지 않아?
This is actually good...
로스가 없어져도 예비로
하나 있으니까 괜찮겠다
... because if we lose Ross,
we have a spare.
네가 그 고생물 학자?
Oh! You are the paleontologist.
그래, 맞아
그런 넌...
Yes. Yes, I am.
And you are a....
Periodontist.
치근 치료사야
See? Now they're as
different as night and...
화석이랑 치석이랑은
완전히 다른 거라고
...Iater that night.
난 뭐 좀 마셔야겠다
Well, I am going to get a beverage.
It was nice meeting you.
- 만나서 반가웠어
- 동감
Ditto.
방금 러스와 인사했어
Well, I met Russ.
우리 사이에 딴사람이
생길 줄은 몰랐어
Hey, I didn't know
we were seeing other people.
우린 아무 사이도 아니잖아
Well, we're not
seeing each other, so....
For your information,
there's a woman at the museum...
혹시나 해서 말해 주는데
박물관에 나방과...
...who's curator of moths and other...
날개 달린 곤충 연구하는
큐레이터가 있는데
...winged things...
내게 관심이 아주 많다고
떠들고 다니더라고
...who's let it be known that
she is drawn to me, much like a...
...you know.
I've kept her at bay,
but if this is the deal
지금까지는 멀리했는데
네가 이렇게 나오면...
This is the deal.
- 그래, 이럴 거야
- 알았어, 데이트 잘해
Okay, well, have a nice evening.
- 러스, 준비됐어?
- 그럼
Russ, you ready?
- 안녕
- 잘 가
남자가 생겼어?
She's dating?
남자가 생겼어!
그래, 지금 보고도 몰라?
Yes, but did you see
who she was dating?
무슨 소리야?
What do you mean?
-Do you not see it?
-See what?
- 못 느꼈어?
- 뭘?
저런 멍청이가 뭐가
좋다고 그러지?
I don't know what she sees
in that goober!
어떻게 표현할까...
It takes him, what?
Like, I don't know...
말 한 마디를 하려면
한 일주일 걸리나?
... hello, a week
to get out a sentence?
It's annoying, isn't it?
너도 짜증나지?
그래!
오디션에는 떨어졌고
이탈리아 국민들이 배고프대?
You didn't get the part...
...or ltaly called
and said it was hungry?
The part's mine if I want it.
맘만 먹으면
배역을 딸 수는 있어
Oh, my God!
잘됐네!
캐스팅 담당하고
하룻밤 자면 된다고
If I'm willing to sleep
with the casting lady.
오 마이...
세상에나!
Oh, my...
...God?
Ten years I've been waiting
for a break like this. Ten years!
이런 기회를 잡으려고
무려 10년을 기다렸어!
I mean, Days of our Lives.
That's actually on television!
'우리들의 삶'은
TV에도 방영되잖아
What are you gonna do?
- 어떻게 할 거야?
- 그 여자랑 자면...
I guess I could sleep with her.
I mean....
How can I do that?
그걸 어떻게 해?
I've got a pop-up book that told me
everything I need to know.
성교육 책자 빌려 줄까?
I've never slept
with someone for a part.
배역을 따내기 위해서
섹스를 한 적은 없어
혹시 그 여자...
Well, is she
Sorry.
미안해
Is she good-looking?
- 얼굴은 괜찮아?
- 그래, 아주 미인이야
She's totally good-looking.
If I met her in a bar...
만약 술집에서 만났으면
아침도 사 주겠어
... I'd be buying her breakfast.
After having slept with her.
둘이 긴 밤을 지내고
심각하게 생각할 거 없네
Maybe this isn't such a big deal.
배역도 따내고 여자도
얻을 기회라고!
The way that I see it is, you get a
great job, and you get to have sex!
Throw in a tree and a fat guy,
and you've got Christmas!
님도 보고 뽕도 따고
바로 그거잖아!
그래도 이런 식은 싫어
I just don't think that
I want it that way, though.
그렇게 해서 성공하면
후에 내 재능이었는지
I mean, let's say
I do make it, all right?
I'll always look back and wonder
if it was because of my talent or...
아님 장군님 때문인지
항상 회의를 할 거라고
...you know, the little general.
Didn't you used to call it
"the little major"?
전엔 '시장님'이라고
부르지 않았어?
After Denise DeMarco,
I had to promote it.
드니스를 만나고 나서
승진시켰어
Something from the bar?
- 술 드릴까요?
- 좋죠
Yes, I would like something.
No. No, thank you.
아뇨, 괜찮아요
If you wanna drink, it's okay with me.
I've gotta get used to it.
마시고 싶으면 마셔
난 괜찮다고
No, no, really.
I wouldn't feel right about it.
아냐, 내가 미안하잖아
물 주세요
Just some water, please.
- 냉장고 불이 나갔는데...
- 스카치 얼음 띄워서요!
-So my refrigerator light's out.
-Scotch on the rocks with a twist!
We're having some fun now, huh, Ross?
아주 재밌지, 로스?
하나 더 할까, 러스?
Wanna do another one?
Huh, Russ?
좋아, '븀'으로 끝나는
원소기호 101번은?
Eleven letters...
...atomic element number 101,
ends in "ium."
Dysprosium.
'디스프로븀'
'디스프로븀' 좋아하네
Try mendelevium.
'멘델레븀'일 거야
And weenie number two has it.
2번과도 연결되는 거야
모르면 9번의 세로...
Unless "Knights in White Satin"
was sung by the Doody Blues.
두디 블루스가 부른
노래의 제목은?
보고도 모르겠어?
You don't see it?
You actually don't see it?
What?
뭘?
넌 로스를 사귀고 있어
Honey, you're dating Ross.
아니, 난 러스와 사귄다고
No, Pheebs, I'm dating Russ.
Russ is Ross. Russ, Ross.
러스가 로스잖아
러스나 로스나!
Steve, sleeve.
스티브와 슬리브는?
'슬리브'란 이름은 없어
No one is named sleeve.
What are you talking about?
대체 뭘 갖고 그래?
이름 비슷한 것 빼고는
뭐가 문제인지 모르겠어
Other than their names being similar,
I do not see what you're seeing.
For your information...
정확한 이름은
'카드사기꾼'이지
...it's a card sharp,
not a card shark.
'카드도박꾼'이 아냐
You could not be more wrong.
말도 안 되는 소리
You could try,
but you would not be successful.
빗나가도 너무나 한참
빗나갔다고
I'm gonna get some more coffee before
the pinching and eye-poking begins.
둘이 할퀴기 전에
난 커피나 더 마실래
I know your problem.
네 문제가 뭔지 알지
Oh, you do, do you?
그러셔?
You're jealous.
질투하는 거야
뭘 질투해?
Of what?
내가 진짜 박사라는 걸
시기하는 것이지
You're jealous
because I'm a real doctor.
Hey, you're a doctor of gums.
넌 잇몸 박사야
That's the smallest body part
you can major in.
우리 신체 부위 중에서
가장 작은 곳이라고
하루만 공부하면
학위를 주는 분야잖아
Day one, floss.
Day two, here's your diploma.
- 잘 들어
- 아니, 말 안 끝났어
You listen here
-Let me finish.
-No, let me finish.
- 아니, 내 말부터 들어
- 마저 들으라니까
No, you let me fin
안녕
아냐... 이건 아냐!
- 조이가 어떻게 할지 알아?
- 몰라
Did Joey say what he was gonna do?
I don't even think he knew.
본인도 모르는 걸 뭐
Would you sleep with somebody
to get a great job?
대단한 일자리를 준다면
누구랑 잘 수 있어?
Who would I have to sleep with?
글쎄...
누구랑 자야 하는데?
Me.
나
Why with you?
왜 내가 너랑 자야 돼?
내 맘이야
잘 거야, 말 거야?
It's my game.
You want the job or not?
Good morning.
- 굿모닝
- 어디 가?
Where you going?
바비와 주말여행 간다고
전에 말했잖아
Bobby and I are going away
for the weekend. Remember?
What's with all the liquor?
술은 왜 가져가?
What's going on?
Is Bobby drinking again?
바비가 다시 술을
마시기 시작했어?
This is not for him.
This is for me.
아냐, 내가 마시려고
그래야 바비의 얘기를
들어 줄 수 있거든
That way, he's sober but his
shoelace stories are more amusing.
노크하는 소리도 정말
따분하네!
God! Even his knock is boring!
-I'll be ready in a second.
-Could I talk to you?
- 금방 나갈게
- 잠깐 얘기 좀 할까?
Sure.
그래
This is hard for me to say.
얘기하기가 힘든데
이런, 또 술 마셨어?
You fell off the wagon!
Oh, no, no.
아니, 너에 대해서야
It's about you.
내가 뭘?
What about me?
I think you may have
a drinking problem.
술을 너무 많이 마시잖아
What, these?
이것 때문에 그래?
이건 소독약 대용이야
No, these are for cuts and scrapes.
Look, I'm not strong enough to be
in a codependent relationship.
서로 의존하는 관계는
나로선 너무 벅차
Oh, shoot.
어머!
Well, anyway,
I hope we can be friends.
- 친구로 지냈으면 좋겠어
- 그래
- 잘지내
- 너도
Take care.
-You too.
-Goodbye.
What happened?
무슨 일이야?
헤어진 것 같아
We kind of broke up.
Does anybody want these?
마실 사람?
I'll take one.
나 하나 줘
Sometimes I hold stuff like this
and pretend I'm a giant.
요만한 거 들고
거인처럼 느껴 보려고
How'd the callback go?
오디션은 어떻게 됐어?
It was unbelievable. I walked
in there and she was all over me.
굉장했어
실내로 들어가자마자
여자가 덤벼들잖아
-What did you do?
-I couldn't do it.
- 그래서 어떡했어?
- 도저히 못하겠더라
I didn't want the part that way.
'이렇게는 안 합니다! '라고
소리쳤지
- 잘했어!
- 아직 안 끝났어
Good for you!
But wait!
I left her office...
사무실을 나와서는
승강기 앞에서 마주쳤는데
...and she caught up with me
and offered me a bigger part.
- 더 큰 배역을 제안하잖아
- 그래서?
So, and?
그래서...
내가 신경외과 의사인
라모레이 박사가 됐어
So, you are now looking at
Dr. Drake Ramoray, neurosurgeon...
최소한 4편의 출연을
보장받았다고!
... recurring in
at least four episodes!
- 축하해!
- 나 샤워하고 올게
All right, I gotta go shower.
- 안녕
- 어서 와
I guess you guys heard
Rachel dumped me.
다들 들었겠지만
레이첼이 날 찼어
Yeah, I'm sorry, man.
그래, 유감이야
내가 누구랑 너무 많이
닮았다고 하던데
She said I remind her
too much of somebody.
Any idea who
she's talking about?
혹시 누군지 알아?
내가 알아
밥 사겟이야
Oh, I do. It's Bob Saget.
아주 싫어하거든
She hates him.
안녕?
Hey, Julie!
- 줄리!
- 어떻게 지냈어?
How are you doing?
I don't know. It's weird
not being with Ross...
로스와 헤어지고 나서
허전하기도 하지만
... but I guess I'm doing okay.
그럭저럭 지내고 있어
Actually, I've got some
of his stuff that he....
로스가 집에 두고 간
물건들이 있어서...